Thank you for waiting.
お待たせ
I waited.
待ったよ
Sorry, I'm so late.
ごめん、めっちゃ遅れた
Yeah, okay.
うん、いいよ
long time no see.
久しぶり
How have you been?
元気だった?
I'm really fine.
めちゃめちゃ元気
I didn't get to see you at all.
全然会えなかったね
Yeah, we've become good friends.
うん、仲良くなったな
Don't you love Ray?
レイの大好きじゃない?
That's about it.
これくらい
You're cute again.
可愛くなったね、また
Am I not good friends?
俺、仲良くないの?
This is today, what is this?
これ、今日ね、何これ?
It's red.
赤いね
Wait, it's right there.
ちょっと、そこだもんか
real?
ほんと?
Yeah, does it suit you?
うん、似合う?
It suits you so well.
めっちゃ似合う
Hey, look, look, pa.
ちょ、見して見して、パって
Wow!
うわ!
cute.
可愛い
I have a date for snack today.
おやつは今日デートなんだけど
What, where do you want to go?
何、行きたいとこある?
Eh, I wonder where it is.
えー、どこだろう
As long as you're going with me, anywhere is fine.
一緒に行くんだったら、どこでもいい
No, wait, what is that?
いや、ちょっと、何それ
what?
何?
Why, because it's embarrassing.
なんで、恥ずかしいから
I'm going to a hotel.
ホテル行っちゃうじゃん
Hey.
ね え
That's the point.
そういうとこだぞ
Well then, let's walk, okay?
じゃあ、歩こうか、じゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Well, it was really, really painful.
いやー、ちょっと、マジめっちゃ痛かったからさ
What have you been doing up until now?
なんか、どうしてたの、今まで
What were you doing?
何してた?
I was restraining myself.
自粛してた
I was properly restrained.
ちゃんと自粛してたよ
That's great.
えらいね
After all, that was also the reason why I wasn't able to see him for a while.
やっぱ、それもあって、ちょっと会えなかったのもあるからね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそう そう
Mess up the little one.
ちっちゃい子をめちゃめちゃ
It's nothing.
なんでもない
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Embarrassing, amazing.
恥ずかしい、すごい
Do you have a small child?
ちっちゃい子いるって?
I'm not doing anything weird right now.
別に、別に今、変なことしないじゃん
Well, that's true, though.
いやー、そうだけどね
There's no connection between that time.
その間ってなんてつながないよ
How long has it been since we held hands?
手つないのどんくらいぶりなんで?
It's been a month since we held hands.
手 つないだのは、1ヶ月で
oh.
お ー
Let's have some fun today.
ちょっと今日はさ、楽しんじゃうぜ
fun.
楽しみ
I have a cold.
風邪が
I have a strong cold.
風邪強いね
風邪強い
Isn't there somewhere you want to go?
行きたいとこないの?
Something.
なんか
Eh, where is it?
え、どこだろう?
It's like I want to go there.
行ってみたいなみたいな
Aquarium.
水族館
Ah, an aquarium.
あ、水族館ね
I'll look into it.
調べてみるわ
Did you do it?
やった?
Yeah.
うん
I looked into it, but it seems like they don't have an aquarium.
調べたんだけど、水族館やってないみたい
Oh, that's a lie?
え、うそー?
Because it's this time of year.
なんか、この時期だから
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
Is there really nothing?
ほんまになんかない?
Huh, what is it?
え、なんだろう?
I haven't been to an amusement park or anything.
遊園地とか全部やってないわ
Ah, so that's over there?
あ、じゃああれはあそこなんだっけ?
Manga for sure.
漫画きっと
teeth?
は?
Because there's something I want to read.
読みたいもんがあるから
It's a date, it's just a date.
デートで、デートじゃん一応
It's kind of more fun.
なんかもっと楽しい
But, I haven't done it.
でもね、やってないから
Even if I did it for fun, I didn't do it.
楽しいとこやったってやってない
I definitely want to go to all kinds of manga.
なんで漫画きっとなんでも行きたい
Oh, I want to read manga.
え、漫画読みたい
comics?
漫画?
yes.
そう
Ah, here comes the manga.
あ、漫画来たんだ
Yes, the manga I wanted to read was not sold in stores at all.
そう、読みたい漫画がね、全然お店に売ってなくて
What came?
何が来たの?
I wonder what it is.
なんだろう
Well, what I want in a manga right now is
えっとね、今漫画で欲しいなって思ってるのは、
Well, there are a lot of them.
なんだ、えーいっぱいあるよ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
There are a lot of them.
いっぱいあるよ
Shall we go in a little while?
ちょっとじゃあ行くか
I did it.
やった
For reading manga.
漫画読みに
Yeah.
うん
OK
I have a bit of a strong cold.
ちょっと風邪も強いしな
yes.
そう
It's cold.
寒いもん
Because it's cold.
寒いからね
It's cold.
寒いよ
OK, let's go.
OK、行こっか
Let's buy something. What do you want to eat?
なんか買ってさ、何食べたい?
something.
何か
I wonder what it is.
何だろう
Hamburger, oh, there's a hamburger.
ハンバーガー、あ、ハンバーガーあるよ
Over there.
あそこに
ah.
あー
Shall we eat a hamburger?
ハンバーガー食べよっか
Well then, let's try it.
じゃあ食べてみよっか
OK, let's go for a bit.
OK、ちょっと行こっか
It's fun.
楽しいな
Also, today is about that.
あと今日はその、あれだから
what?
何?
Because it's next door.
お隣だから
Yeah.
うん
Because I'm taking photos of hotels.
ホテル撮ってるから
what?
何?
It's a nice shot of the hotel.
いい感じでホテル撮ってるから
Yeah.
うん
Already today.
今日はもう
I like it.
気に入ってる
Let's have fun.
楽しもうね
Yeah.
うん
Okay.
よし
let's go.
行 こう
Yay.
やっ
It's here.
来たね
Because it's my first time here.
初めて来たから
Yeah.
うん
Where is it?
何所のとこなの?
There were a lot of manga at the entrance.
なんか漫画は入り口にめっちゃいっぱいあったけど
It was there.
あったっしょ
there were.
あった
yes.
そう
It's like a manga cafe,
それは漫画喫茶っていう具合だから、
Isn't this where you read manga?
漫画を読むとこなんじゃない?
It's all you can read.
読み放題なのね
Do you like manga?
漫画好き?
I really like manga.
漫画めっちゃ好き
But it's like the whole country, okay?
でも全国みたいなとこじゃん、じゃあ
yes.
そう
I'll read it later.
あとで読もう
What do you like, comics?
何が好きなの、漫画は?
Well, lately I've been using the free line.
えっとね、最近は自由使い線
ah.
ああ
yes.
そう
I already have everything on my phone.
携帯にね、もう全部入ってる
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
yes.
そう
If it's a book, there's no place to put it.
本だと置くとこないから
I tend to watch it on my phone.
携帯で見る派なんだ
I like to watch it on my cell phone.
携帯で見る派
Also, the manga I collected were Attack on Titan and Black Sheep.
あとは、漫画で集めてたのは、進撃の巨人と黒羊
I really love drawing.
絵がめちゃめちゃ好きで
I was collecting.
集めてた
There are a lot of girls who like girls, they call them black sheep.
女の子好きな子多いよね、あれを黒羊って
cool.
かっこいい
Isn't it cool?
かっこいいでしょ?
cool.
かっこいい
Something like that here.
なんかあれだよ、ここ
It's a completely private room.
完全に個室だね
It's a private room.
個室だね
Don't you have a camera?
カメラとかないの?
Would it be bad if there was?
あったらやばいのか?
No, of course.
ないっしょ、それはさすがに
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
It may have been reached.
到達されてるかもしれない
No way.
やだー
Well, eat.
まあ、食べる
The one I bought.
買ってきたやつ
I bought it, so I'm going to eat it.
買 ってきたから食べるよ
What I was eating.
食べ てたやつ
Are you hungry?
お腹すいたっしょ?
I'm hungry.
お腹すいた
I'm hungry, so I'm hungry.
お 腹すいたから、お腹すいた
What are you saying?
何だよ、こう言ってるの
This is cute.
かわいいな、これ
cute.
かわいい
Like, kind of.
いいね、なんか
Awesome, so cute.
すごい、かわいい
It's called a date.
デートって言うんだよね
It's a date though.
デートなんだけど
It's a date.
デートだよ
I'm taking pictures of the hotel today, so it's night.
今日ホテル撮ってるから、夜
I can stay the night, so today.
泊まれるから、今日
What kind of place is it?
どんなところなんだろう?
It feels pretty good.
結構いい感じの
It's early.
早いね
fun?
楽しみ?
Yeah.
うん
I'll eat it.
食べ ちゃうよね
Shall I eat it?
食べちゃう?
You'll eat it.
食べちゃうよね
Isn't it nearby?
近くない?
Something.
なんか
It's not like that.
なんかじゃない
Something like that.
なんかね
Shall I bring some comics?
なんか漫画持ってこようか
read?
読む?
If you read it, you'll probably fall in love with it.
読んだら、夢中になっちゃう、多分
Are you going crazy?
夢中になっちゃう?
It's no longer a tradition.
伝統どころじゃなくなっちゃう
now?
今は?
It tickles, so much.
くすぐったい、めっちゃ
It's so ticklish.
めちゃくすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
I don't know.
わかんない
It's more itchy than ticklish.
くすぐったいって言うより、かゆい
itch?
かゆい?
It's itchy.
かゆくなる
yes?
そう?
this?
これ?
It's so amazing, I'm so horny.
なんかさ、すげえさ、ムラムラする
why?
なんで?
It's still noon.
まだお昼だよ
Lunch?
お昼?
It's cute, really.
可愛いよ、ほんと
It's been a while, so it's amazing.
久しぶりだからさ、すごい
It's so fuzzy, kind of.
めちゃめちゃ羽ばしい、なんか
lie?
うそ?
It's been a long time, I guess.
すげえ久しぶりだな、なんか
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
Something like that.
なんかさ
why?
なんで?
I haven't been able to meet you recently.
最近会えなかったじゃん
Because it's a time like this.
こういう時期だから
I'm eating.
食べてるよ
picture?
え?
I'm eating.
食べてるよ
Hey.
ねえ
Are you eating?
食べてる?
I'm eating.
食べてる
Can I eat too?
俺も食べていい?
What do you eat?
何食べるの?
You're doing your best.
頑張ってんね
Why are you eating?
なんで食べてる?
Really.
ほんとに
Because I can't swallow it.
飲み込めないからね
Can I eat it?
食べていい?
Something like that.
なんかね
yeah?
ん?
Because I can't swallow it.
飲み込めないから
Hey.
ねえ
Really.
ほんとに
Swallow it, right?
飲み込めでしょ
I can't drink it.
飲めないな
Hey.
ねえ
Oh, is it really a one-piece dress?
あ、すごくワンピースなの?
It's one piece.
ワンピースなの
This dress is so cute for me.
すごい可愛いよ、俺この服
real?
ほんと?
a little bit?
ちょっと?
He said it was candy.
飴てるって言ってんだよ
He says it's okay to eat.
食べていいって言うから
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しいでしょ
美味 しいでしょ
Are you eating?
食べてるの?
食べ てるの?
Because I can't swallow it.
飲み込めないから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Half center.
半中
Did you eat it?
食べたし?
I ate it.
食べたし
It's still in my arms.
まだ 腕の中入ってる
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
Yeah.
うん
show me.
見せて
a.
あ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
It's not good at all.
なんも良くない
Hey, don't try too hard.
ちょ、もうさ、頑張らないで
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Disgusting.
嫌な
show me.
見せて
No.
ダメ
Good.
よいしょ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
No.
ダメ
not present.
いない
Don't.
いけません
Hey.
ねえ
What are you doing?
何してんの?
a little bit.
ちょっと
If you read the manga, you won't come here, right?
漫画読むとこないんでしょ、やってここ
It's not just about reading comics.
漫画読むだけじゃないよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Because.
だってさ
Yeah.
うん
what?
何?
Don't read comics.
漫画読むんじゃないよ
It's okay because they won't come in.
入 ってこないから大丈夫だよ
Because I wanted to.
だってしたかったっしょ
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Hey.
ねえ
a little bit.
ちょっと
what?
何?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
This is no good.
こうはダメ
That's good.
いい じゃん
Not anymore, right?
もうねえでしょ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
No.
ダメだよ
ダメ
It's not okay.
ダメじゃないの
It's not good at all.
なんもよくないでしょ
amazing.
すごい
It's not bad, right?
ダメじゃないでしょ
No.
ダメ
It's been a while since I saw it.
久々に見た
what?
何?
What is this cushion?
何このクッション?
a little bit.
ちょっと
what?
何?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
amazing.
すごい
terrible.
やばい
I'm a little impressed
ちょっと感激してる
circle.
わ
There's something.
何 かある
It's beautiful.
綺麗だな
What should I do?
どうする?
I wish someone was watching this.
これ誰か見てたら
That's no good, right?
ダメでしょ
There might be a camera or something.
カメラとかあるかもしれない
what?
何?
It's late.
遅いって
Just look, just look.
見るだけ見るだけ
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
You're sleeping a lot.
すごい寝るしてるじゃん
You wanted to, right?
したかったでしょ
You're making a sound.
声出してるね
yeah?
ん?
No?
ダメ?
Kuchokuchoyo.
くちょくちょよ
I was bored.
くちょくちょした
Impossible.
無理
No?
ダメ?
You should sleep here.
こっち寝たほうがいいでしょ
こっち寝たほうがいいよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Are you feeling good?
気 持 ち いい?
No.
ダメ
Let's go together.
おけいっしょ
Here!
こら!
Actually.
本当には
You were too loud.
声出しすぎたな
Who is to blame?
誰のせいですか?
Sorry for a second.
ちょっと、ごめんな
Well, I'm taking pictures of the battery today.
じゃ、バッテリー撮ってるから今日
picture?
え?
Battery-san is taking pictures at night.
バッテリーさん夜撮ってるから
Yeah.
うん
Hey, let's take it easy.
ちょっとね、ゆっくりしよう
Okay.
いいっしょ
What did you do?
何したの?
What are you doing?
何してんの?
I'm brushing my teeth since I'm going to bed.
寝るから歯磨いてるの
sorry.
ごめん
Can I take a picture?
ちょっと撮っていい?
Because I'm brushing my teeth.
歯磨いてるから
I'm not sleeping.
寝てない
That doesn't make any sense.
そんな意味ないよ
cute.
かわいい
How was your day?
今日どうだった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
it was fun?
楽しかった?
Yeah.
うん
why?
なんで?
It's cute.
かわいいね
a little bit.
ちょっと
picture?
え?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Sorry if I sleep.
寝するとごめんなさい
Are you asleep?
寝せいだ?
Yes, I'm sleeping.
うん、寝せいだ
Well then, let's go to sleep.
じゃあ、寝よっか
what?
なに?
Are you going to sleep?
寝るんでしょ?
how was it?
どうだった?
today.
今日
It was fun.
楽しかったよ
it was fun?
楽しかった?
Yeah.
うん
It’s been a while?
久々だった?
It's been a while.
久しぶりだったね
It's been a month.
1ヶ月あったね
Yeah.
うん
We hadn't met.
会ってなかったもんね
Didn't you have sex during that time?
その間、エッチしなかった?
I haven't.
してない
Haven't you?
してないの?
Yeah, I haven't.
うん、 してない
It’s been a while since Chuu too?
チュウも久しぶり?
Yeah, it's been a while.
うん、久しぶり
It's cute, really.
かわいいね、ほんと
It's not cute.
かわいくない
So you weren't having sex at all?
じゃあ、全然エッチしてなかったの?
I didn't.
してなかった
What were you doing during that time?
その間、どうしてたの?
Stab me.
刺してよ
What do you mean by stabbing?
刺してってどういうこと?
Stab me.
刺してよ
So I left it alone.
だから、1人で捨てたの
Seriously?
マジ?
Because it was delicious.
美味しかったから
Seriously?
マジで?
real.
ほんと
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
It's cute.
かわいいですね
It was delicious.
美味しかったんだ
美味しかった
Wow.
すーって
す ーって
It's embarrassing, but there you go.
恥ずかしいんだけど、そこ
It's so embarrassing.
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしいんだ
It's been a while since I touched it.
久々に触るからさ
touch?
触れる?
what?
何?
Did it come out?
出てきた?
Don't leave it alone.
放置しないで
It's really embarrassing, just leave it like this.
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしいよ、このままじゃ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
touch?
触れる?
It came out.
出てきた
close.
近い
It's close.
近いよ
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
恥ずかしいでしょ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
You look amazing.
すごい顔してるね
Is that so?
そうかな?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気 持ちいい?
Do you feel good?
気 持 ちいい?
when
当
Do you have it?
た ってる?
I guess.
当てますけど
lie?
嘘?
It's not a lie.
嘘じゃない
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気 持ちいい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気 持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
amazing.
すごい
Open it yourself.
自分で開いて
I got up.
起き上がった
what?
何?
Open Mank.
マンク開いて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
close.
近い
It's pretty close.
だいぶ近いよ
close?
近い?
It's pretty close.
だいぶ近いよ
Can you see clearly?
はっきり見える?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だな
Can I close my hands?
手閉めていい?
No.
ダメ
why?
なんで?
Is it still bad?
まだダメなの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I went here.
ここへ行っちゃった
sorry.
ごめん
Did it take?
かかった?
It took a lot of time.
めっちゃかかった
It was dripping.
垂れちゃった
Really.
本当に
Did it take?
かかった?
It was really here.
めっちゃここあった
sorry.
ごめん
Why did you go?
なん で行っちゃったの?
some time ago.
さっき
Did you go to your seat?
席に行っちゃったの?
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい